mydeal.com.au 2018-08-17

# Privacy Policy

MyDeal.com.au (“Site”) is owned and operated by E-COM (Aus) Pty Ltd, ABN 60 150 104 715 (“MyDeal”).

MyDeal respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information in accordance with the National Privacy Principles of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). Personal information broadly means information or an opinion about an individual whose identity is apparent, or can be reasonably ascertained from that information or opinion. Our Privacy Policy sets out MyDeal’s policies relating to the collection and use of your personal information. It applies to your conduct on the Site and by using the Site, you agree to and consent to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information by MyDeal according to this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy is in addition to the Terms and Conditions governing the Site and should be read in conjunction with the Terms and Conditions.   

For more information on privacy in Australia, please refer to the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner [website](https://www.oaic.gov.au/). 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via our contact us page [_here_](https://help.mydeal.com.au/hc/en-us). 

When you visit the Site, MyDeal will operate the Site according to the following:

#### Personal Information

MyDeal collects personal information for the purposes of carrying on its business as an online platform for the sale of goods and services (including on behalf of third party merchants). The type of information we collect will vary depending on the nature of your dealings with MyDeal. Personal information that we generally collect may include your name, address, email address, telephone number and payment details. 

There are two main ways we collect information about you: 

#### If you are not or do not login as a MyDeal Member

Whenever you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information about your usage of the Site, such as the time of your visit, its duration and the pages you visit. This is to help us understand what parts of the Site our users enjoy the most and to help us ensure that advertisements on the Site are most directly relevant to your interests. If you have not identified yourself on the Site, such as by registering for Membership or logging in as a Member, the information we collect about you remains anonymous. 

#### If you login as a MyDeal Member

When you first register for membership, we collect information from you such as your email, name, suburb, and will continue to add to your member profile as you interact more on the Site, for example, if you enter a competition.   

Once you have become a registered member, we collect personal information about you in order to provide you with the full benefits of Membership. It will also enable MyDeal to bill you and contact you, where necessary, concerning your use of the Site. MyDeal will also use and analyse the information it collects so that it can administer, support, improve and develop our business.   
In particular, MyDeal may contact you for your views on the Site and also to notify you about changes or developments to the Site and services. If you have consented, we may also use your information in order to advise you about other products and services which we offer. 

#### How we preserve your privacy

MyDeal will maintain any information in strict confidence and only use this information in connection with the aforementioned purposes, including providing your relevant details to third party merchants for either (i) the delivery/provision of goods or services ordered or (ii) for the redemption of vouchers you bought. 

MyDeal does not collect sensitive information beyond information outlined above about users. Your personal information will not be shared, sold, rented, or disclosed other than as described in this privacy policy. 

#### Security of Your Information

MyDeal takes all reasonable steps to ensure that sensitive information that MyDeal collects is only accessible by authorised persons and there is no misuse of personal information. We will retain your information for a reasonable time or as long as the law requires. 

No transmission over the Internet can be 100% secure and although MyDeal will take reasonable steps to protect information transmission, MyDeal cannot guarantee the integrity of transmission over the internet and to the maximum extent permitted by law, MyDeal will not be liable for any breach relating to information transmission. 

#### Third Parties

Your personal sensitive information and data is only shared with third parties at your direction or in connection with your use of the Site (including in relation to your purchases of goods/services and/or vouchers) or as is required or permitted by law. This may include instances where we are required to transmit personal information according to instructions received from a law enforcement agency or other authorised body.   

Where MyDeal does make information or data available to certain authorised agents of MyDeal, it will do so only in connection with the operation of the Site and MyDeal will ensure that they apply the MyDeal Privacy Policy or in applicable statutory or common law requirement. MyDeal will not pass your information on to advertisers except with your permission.   

Please note that in using the Site you may be communicating with individuals and organisations outside of Australia. In that case, their use of your personal information may not be covered by Australian law or an applicable privacy protection scheme. 

#### Secure Online Transactions

If you purchase Product(s) or Voucher(s) (as defined in our terms and conditions) through our Site, we process your credit card details securely over the Internet using eWAY’s bank-grade data centre (eWAY is a tier-one PCI DSS compliant payment gateway). We employ a 256 Bit SSL Certificate on our Site to ensure that your credit card and anonymity are protected when you purchase online. If you opt in to save your card, eWay will retain your credit card details on its servers for future purchases on MyDeal. MyDeal does not store your credit card details. 

#### Non-customer information

Sometimes, MyDeal needs to collect personal information about individuals who are not Account holders or customers. This will usually arise where we collect the name and business contact details of a person who is the contact in a government agency or company with whom we deal. MyDeal’s policy is to only use personal information collected from non-customers for the main business purpose for which it was collected. 

#### Changing Your Information

If you are a MyDeal Member, you are able to view and amend your Personal Information stored by MyDeal at all times. MyDeal will not amend your personal information except at your direction. 

#### Unsubscribing from email subscriptions

From time-to-time MyDeal.com.au may send you electronic marketing material - but only ever in accordance with the provisions of Spam Act 2003 (Cth). 

You may unsubscribe from our mailing list at any time:

1\. Open any newsletter sent to you by MyDeal.com.au.  
2\. Scroll to the bottom of the newsletter and click 'Unsubscribe'. 

#### 18 Years of Age

Unless special agreement has been made with MyDeal, Members of the Site must be at least 18 years of age. 

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small file which is placed on the user’s hard drive following a visit to the Site. This file subsequently allows the user to move quickly and easily around the Site by keeping a record of your previous visit(s). It is used to identify users and tracks a user’s sessions providing information that the system used to efficiently manage your use of the site. We do not link this information to user’s personal details. Cookies can be deleted from a user’s hard drive at any time by the user. 

#### Changes to this Policy

MyDeal may amend this Privacy Policy wholly or partly from time to time without providing notice. The amended Privacy Policy will be effective from the time it is uploaded on the Site. 

#### How to contact MyDeal

If you would like to make an access request to your personal information or wish to provide feedback about this policy, please contact MyDeal via our contact us page [here](https://help.mydeal.com.au/hc/en-us) **or by mail at MyDeal.com.au PO Box 4350, Doncaster Heights, VIC 3019.**
